<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Buschfunk Project</title>
    <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Buschfunk Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 17:47:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://buschfunkproject.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 17:47:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Chat, discuss and collaborate:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:53:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A brief overview of the project and its goals can be found in this short video.
Defintion of Buschfunk   German slang for a gossip network A system used by undeveloped societies in remote regions for communication over long distances, such as drum sounds, word-of-mouth relay, or smoke signals.  Similar bush telegraph
 About the Project We want to provide free and open-source solutions to serve as a foundation for communication technology in challenged environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:53:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/architecture/</guid>
      <description>All components of the funky Buschfunk Project orchestra are briefly described in the following.
Drumsticks - Apps Apps can be easily written an deployed as Progressive Web Applications (PWA) using our core libraries as Web Assembly modules or deployed as native code directly on devices.
Tomborine - LoRa Companion Device These small devices can be used stand alone to receive data such as text messages but can also be paired with a smartphone, tablet or laptop using Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) to increase communication range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:53:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>Firmwares   Tamborine - rf95modem firmware Basic firmware for ESP32 and Cortex M0 based boards to make LoRa functionality available via USB-Serial, WiFi and BLE.
  Bongo - ESP32 T-Beam Image not yet released
  Conga - Raspberry Pi Image not yet released
  LoRa   rf95modem firmware Basic firmware for ESP32 and Cortex M0 based boards to make LoRa functionality available via USB-Serial, WiFi and BLE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 16:53:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buschfunkproject.github.io/media/</guid>
      <description>Buschfunk Project Overview   DTN Explained   Buschfunk Project Architecture   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>